

# Axy David Copenhagen, Denmark

My Portfolio: axydavid.com

axy david@yahoo.com

in

linkedin.com/in/axy-david

#### Hi! I'm David!

- 7+ years experience and Seniority in UI/UX Design, Full-Stack Development, and Software Consultancy.
- Extensive experience with startups, small and mid-sized companies.
- Experience managing projects from the conceptual stage through to the final delivery.
- Highly autonomous, self-sufficient, eager to take initiative.
- Proficient in React, TypeScript, JavaScript, PHP, Node, SQL, HTML/CSS, Figma, Adobe Creative Suite,
   Wordpress & more

I excel in project execution. Collaborating closely with clients, I strive to deeply understand their needs and develop them into successful web solutions. My expertise lies in starting projects from scratch, designing and developing intuitive user interfaces, and implementing them with the appropriate technology.

Throughout my career, I have created web solutions for a variety of clients, earning project management expertise and industry-specific knowledge.

My hobbies are making music, enjoying nature, and hanging out.

#### **Experience**



#### Senior Full Stack Developer & UI/UX Design Specialist

Wayfare

Sep 2022 - Present (1 year)

I design and put ideas into practice for a variety of websites and projects while employed as a full-stack and UX/UI developer. I successfully designed and delivered three websites, ensuring that they aligned with the company's objectives and met the needs of their target audience. Throughout the process, I adjusted the designs based on feedback and worked to create seamless and engaging user experiences.

#### Senior UI/UX Designer & Consultant with Expertise in Full Stack Development

Adooboo Creative

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022 (8 months)

I created web applications that tailored to the clients particular needs after evaluating the client's and the company's target consumers.

Used my expertise in product design to create isometric mockups, brand identities, and advertisement mockups.

Delivered tailored solutions that satisfied clients' or companies' particular niche needs and resonated with the target audience.

## Senior UI/UX Designer & Consultant with Expertise in Full Stack Development

**TotalReward** 

Sep 2020 - Jan 2022 (1 year 5 months)

I had to design and maintain a system seamlessly aiding direct sellers and distributors throughout the sales and marketing process providing features that assist with lead generation, marketing, customer management, inventory, and distribution. I was also supposed to manage a team ensuring a swift and reliable development. I used jQuery, JS, HTML5, CSS for front-end and PHP, for back-end.



#### Software Consultant with Expertise in Full Stack Development & UI/UX Designer UB University

Dec 2019 - Sep 2020 (10 months)

Designed a platform facilitating online exams, tests and practice. Implemented as a web application it was collecting the student responses and gave relevant analytics to the teacher. It also had an algorithm that could, based on the available data give relevant suggestions to both the teacher and the students on how to improve their respective weak areas within their subjects. I used jQuery, JS, HTML5, CSS for front-end and PHP, MySQL for back-end.



#### **Software Developer**

PortaPlay

Apr 2017 - Feb 2018 (11 months)

Developed and implemented a multiplayer experience for an existing game in the Unity engine using C#. Synchronized multiple clients using the photon engine framework.

#### YP Software Consultant with Expertise in Full Stack Development & UI/UX Designer

YourPhoner

Feb 2015 - Jun 2017 (2 years 5 months)

Had to develop a website and implement a customer relationship management system handling all of the business's contacts and interactions with clients and potential leads. I used the WordPress platform for prototyping along with jQuery, JS, HTML5, CSS and PHP.

#### **Education**



### DTU - Technical University of Denmark

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Computer Science and Network Communication



#### ♠ KCM

IT - Line, Information Technology

Studied IT & Electronics along with a science and programming custom programme at KCM High- school.

#### **Skills**

Full-Stack Development • Git • HTML • Product Development • Adobe Illustrator UI/UX design • Agile Methodologies • Figma (Software) • Skill Development • Agile Development